https://thewoodwhisperer.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy for www.thewoodwhisperer.com
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
At thewoodwhisperer.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.thewoodwhisperer.com and how it is used.
Log Files Like many other Web sites, thewoodwhisperer.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons thewoodwhisperer.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.thewoodwhisperer.com.
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to thewoodwhisperer.com and other sites on the Internet.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….
Google Adsense
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.thewoodwhisperer.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
thewoodwhisperer.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.thewoodwhisperer.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of TheWoodWhisperer.com then you may contact us at marc@thewoodwhisperer.com
Sponsors
Advertisers
This is placeholder text
This is placeholder text
This is placeholder text
The Wood Whisperer is proudly sponsored by brands that Marc trusts. Thank you for making this possible.
Mobile-alt
Youtube
Instagram
Facebook-f
Twitter
Rss
Copyright © 2006-2020 The Wood Whisperer Inc. The Wood Whisperer, The Wood Whisperer Guild, TWW, and TWW Guild are trademarks of The Wood Whisperer Inc. All rights reserved. Designed and developed by Underscorefunk Design
Home
About
FAQ
Contact
Disclaimer
Privacy
Menu
Home
About
FAQ
Contact
Disclaimer
Privacy
This site uses affiliate links. Given this, please assume that any links leading you to products or services are affiliate links that we will receive compensation from. However, there are millions of products and services on the web, and I only promote those products or services that I would use personally. The Wood Whisperer abides by word of mouth marketing standards and holds integrity in the highest regard. Should I ever be compensated to write, I will make full disclosure. I always give honest opinions, findings, and experiences on products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely our own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question. All content on The Wood Whisperer is copyrighted, and may not be reprinted in full form without my written consent.
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
